很好，很好，准备周四的比赛。
Good, very good, preparing for the game on Thursday.
Bien, muy bien, preparando el partido el jueves.
显然很高兴再次来到这里。
Obviously happy to be here again.
Contento obviamente de estar otra vez acá.
我们知道这不是一场轻松的比赛，但我们正在做好充分的准备。
We know it is not an easy game, but we are preparing well.
Sabemos que no es un partido fácil, pero nos estamos preparando bien.
这是一个艰难的对手，你必须去那里比赛，这也很艰难。
It's a tough opponent, you have to go play there, it's also tough.
Es un rival duro, hay que ir a jugar allá que también es duro.
您认为巴拉圭会提出什么建议？
What do you imagine this Paraguay is going to propose?
¿Qué te imaginas que es lo que va a proponer este Paraguay?
古斯塔沃的球队对我们来说总是很艰难。
Gustavo's teams were always quite tough for us.
Los equipos de Gustavo siempre fueron bastante duros para nosotros.
他的想法很清晰，信息传达得很好。
He has a clear idea, the message is conveyed very well.
Tiene una idea clara, el mensaje lo transmite muy bien.
在我看来，巴拉圭正处于一个非常好的时刻，他们也刚刚在那里赢得了巴西队的胜利。
It seems to me that Paraguay is in a very good moment, they have just won Brazil there as well.
Me parece que Paraguay está en un muy buen momento, vienen de ganar la Brasil también allá.
所以这将是一场相当艰难的比赛。
So it's going to be a pretty difficult match.
Así que va a ser un partido bastante difícil.
我们将竭尽全力争取三分。
We are going to try to do our best to get the three points.
Vamos a intentar hacer lo mejor para tener los tres puntos.
罗迪戈和巴拉圭一直是让他们付出代价的竞争对手
Ródigo and Paraguay were always a rival that has cost them
Ródigo y Paraguay siempre fue un rival que les ha costado
也许是因为巴拉圭的比赛方式，甚至，好吧，我告诉你，随着灯塔的到来，它的后防线变得更加稳定了。
perhaps because of the way Paraguay plays and even, well, I tell you, with the arrival of the lighthouse it has become a little more, even, solid at the back.
quizás por la forma de jugar que tiene Paraguay e incluso, bueno, les digo, con la llegada del faro se ha hecho un poquito más, inclusive, sólido atrás.
总体来说，各方都在努力。
In general, all parties make an effort.
En general, a nosotros todos los partidos hacemos un esfuerzo.
后来非常大，事实是事情进展得很顺利，但是
very big afterwards the truth is that things went very well but
muy grande después la verdad que las cosas salieron muy bien pero
所有的努力和所有的比赛都让我们付出了代价。
The efforts and all the games cost us.
los esfuerzos y todos los partidos nos cuestan.
正如我告诉你的，古斯塔沃的球队相当困难，巴拉圭是......
As I told you, Gustavo's teams are quite difficult, Paraguay is a...
Como te decía, los equipos de Gustavo son bastante difíciles, Paraguay es un...
嗯，我认为每个球队也都有自己的历史。
Well, I think each team also has its history.
Bueno, creo que cada selección también tiene su historia.
从历史上看，巴拉圭一直是一支非常有侵略性的球队。
Historically, Paraguay has always been a very aggressive team that makes the games.
Paraguay históricamente siempre fue un equipo muy agarrido que hace los partidos.
如果这是一场这种风格的比赛，我们会打得非常好，我认为我们已经准备好了，是的，很好
very fought so well if it's a match of that style I think we are prepared and yes well
muy luchados así que bueno si toca un partido de ese estilo creo que estamos preparados y si bueno
我们可以进行我们的游戏。
we can carry out our game.
podemos llevar a cabo nuestro juego.
欢迎。
Welcome be.
Bienvenido sea.
迪布的回归，显然是一些新人的加入
The return of Dibu, obviously some new guys who join
La vuelta de Dibu, obviamente algunos chicos nuevos que se suman
他们的运气也不好，有伤病，缺席了一些资格赛。
and they are also having bad luck with some injuries, some losses in the qualifying rounds.
y también están teniendo mala suerte con algunas lesiones, algunas bajas en las fechas eliminatorias.
一如既往，这个团队非常好。
The group is super good, as always.
El grupo es súper bien, como siempre.
这对我们来说是一种快乐。
It is a joy for us.
Es una alegría para nosotros.
在这里
be here
estar acá.
我们是真正的一家人。
We are truly a family.
Somos realmente una familia.
我们大多数人已经在那里呆了很多年了，那些即将到来的人
Most of us have been there for many years, those who are coming
La mayoría llevamos muchos años, los que se vienen
合并我认为他们做得很好
Incorporating I think they are doing very well
Incorporando creo que lo están haciendo muy bien
他们是伟大的球员，是的，我们有几次受伤，所有这些。
They are great players and well, yes, we had several injuries, all of these.
que son grandes jugadores y bueno, sí, tuvimos varias lesiones todas estas.
这些电话，但是我认为这有点动态
these calls, but well, I think it's a bit of the dynamic
estas convocatorias, pero bueno, creo que es un poco de la dinámica
那是在足球领域，我们的比赛数量、日历、俱乐部也非常......
that is in football, the number of games we have, the calendars, the clubs are also very...
que está en el fútbol, la cantidad de partidos que tenemos, los calendarios, los clubes también son muy...
市中心。
downtown.
en el centro de la ciudad.
比赛之间的间隔很短，最后身体有时会过去……
They are very short between matches and well, in the end the body sometimes passes...
Son muy cortos entre partido y partido y bueno, al final el cuerpo a veces pasa...
这需要付出代价，但是嘿，无论谁得到它，都会做好充分的准备。
It takes its toll but hey, whoever gets it is going to be super prepared.
pasa factura pero bueno el que le toque va a estar super preparado
罗德里戈，昨天我听说了一个非常特殊的情况，我不知道你是否看到了里斯特拉发生的事情，这个在甲级联赛踢球的流男孩，好吗？
Rodrigo, yesterday I heard about a very particular situation, I don't know if you saw what happened with Riestra, this stream boy playing in the first division, okay?
Rodrigo, ayer se una situación muy particular, no se si viste, lo que paso con Riestra, este chico stream jugando en primera división, ok?
它给你带来了怎样的感受？
What feeling did it give you?
¿Qué sensación te causó?
导致我的原因是...
What causes me is...
A mí lo que me causa es...
我认为最重要的是消息。
I think the most important thing is the message.
Creo que lo más importante es el mensaje.
站在这一边的人必须给予，我认为这不是正确的信息。
He who is on this side has to give and I think that is not the right message.
el que está de este lado tiene que dar y creo que ese no es el mensaje correcto.
在我看来，尽管足球相当偏向一边
It seems to me that although football went to one side quite a bit
Me parece que si bien el fútbol fue para un lado bastante
说到营销这个话题，因为世界似乎冻结了。
with the topic of marketing because well, the world appears frozen.
con el tema del marketing porque bueno, el mundo aparece helado.
这并不一定掩盖我们必须传递信息的事实。
That doesn't have to overshadow the fact that we have to transmit a message.
Eso no tiene que opacar que nosotros tenemos que transmitir un mensaje.
我可以告诉你，因为我也是一个让我付出了很多代价的男孩。
I can tell you because I was also a boy who cost me a lot.
Yo lo puedo contar porque también fui un chico que me costó un montón.
要想在甲级联赛踢球，那不是办法，你必须工作。
to be able to play in the first division, that is not the way, you have to work.
poder llegar a jugar en primera división, que esa no es la manera, hay que trabajar.
你必须强迫自己，你必须跌倒并再试一次。
You have to force yourself, you have to fall and try again.
Hay que forzarse, hay que caer y volver a intentar.
这是成为一名足球运动员必须经历的整个过程的一部分。
It is part of the whole process that one has to go through to be a soccer player.
Es parte de todo el proceso en el que uno tiene que pasar para ser jugador de fútbol.
这就是我们所有人都必须努力传达的信息。
and that is the message that we all have to try to give.
y ese es el mensaje que tenemos que intentar dar todos.
我不同意所发生的事情。
I don't agree with what happened.
No estoy de acuerdo con lo que sucedió.
但更重要的是，我作为阿根廷队向你们重复一遍，我相信
but more than that, I repeat to you as the Argentine team that I believe that
pero más que eso ya te repito nosotros como selección argentina que creo que
还好此时此刻传来这样的消息：
It's good that at this moment the message that
que bueno que en este momento el mensaje que
我们给予的东西将非常重要，因为我们与人民非常接近，因为人们非常认同我们。
What we give is going to be very important because we are very close to the people, because people identify with us a lot.
que demos va a ser muy importante porque estamos muy cerca de la gente, porque la gente se identifica mucho con nosotros.
我们所有在这一边踢球、穿着国家队球衣的人都付出了很多代价，没有人给我们任何东西。
All of us who are on this side to play and wear the national team shirt cost us a lot, no one gave us anything.
Todos los que estamos de este lado para jugar y vestirnos la camiseta de la selección nos costó una barbaridad, nadie nos regaló nada.
这是我所知道并且相信是正确的唯一道路。
and it is the only path that I know and I believe is the correct one.
y es el único camino que yo conozco y creo que es el correcto.
列表
List
Listo.
他说，罗德里戈，我借此机会讨论同样的话题，因为弗里登的这篇文章产生了很大的影响。
He said, Rodrigo, I take this opportunity to take up the same topic because this entry by Frieden had a lot of impact.
Decía, Rodrigo, te aprovecho para tomar el mismo tema porque tuvo mucha repercusión este ingreso de Frieden.
在昨天与里斯特拉斯拉科鲁尼亚队的比赛中，这方面的概念也得到了发展。
in what was yesterday's game of Deportivo Riestras and a concept in this regard is also developed.
en lo que fue el partido de ayer de Deportivo Riestras y también es elaborado un concepto al respecto.
当然，所说的话，我们的想法，或者至少是我和那些与 Dablé 一起的同伴的想法，或多或少......
Surely what was said, our thoughts, or at least mine and the companions with the dablés, are more or less...
Seguramente lo que se dijo, el pensamiento nuestro, o por lo menos mí y los compañeros con los dablés, son más o menos...
这不是例子，这不是我们想传达给年轻人的信息。
The same is not the example, it is not the message that we want to give to the youngest.
Lo mismo, no es el ejemplo, no es el mensaje que queremos dar para los más jóvenes.
为了我必须生活的事情，为了我所见到的那些已经到来的同事，他们在足球上取得了胜利，而那些没有到来的人也做出了很多牺牲。
for what I had to live, for the colleagues that I saw who have arrived, who have triumphed in football and those who have not arrived have made many sacrifices.
por lo que me tocó vivir, por los compañeros que vi que han llegado, que han triunfado en el fútbol y los que no han llegado han hecho muchísimos sacrificios.
能够在甲级联赛中进行比赛并发生这种事情，事实是......
to be able to play a game in the first division and for this type of thing to happen, the truth is that...
para poder jugar un partido en primera división y que pase en este tipo de cosas, la verdad que...
这很烦人，很烦人，因为正如我之前所说，发出这些类型的消息并不好。
That's annoying, annoying because as I said before it's not nice to give those types of messages.
que molesta, molesta porque como dije antes no es lindo dar ese tipo de mensajes.
我也理解，嗯，今天你进来时，这发生在你身上，所有跟随你的小孩子，模仿你所做的事情，在我看来，他们也是这样做的。
I also understand, well, it happened to you today when you came in, all the little ones who follow you, who imitate the things you do, it seems to me that they do too.
entiendo también bueno te pasó hoy a vos cuando entraste todos los chiquitos que lo siguen a ustedes que imitan las cosas que hacen ustedes me parece que también
也可以到那里
can also come there
también puede venir por ahí
是的，显然。
Yes, obviously.
Sí, obviamente.
正如我重复的那样，对我们来说，足球的榜样就是牺牲，就是尊重。
As I repeat, for us the example of football is sacrifice, it is respect.
Como te repito, para nosotros el ejemplo del fútbol es sacrificio, es respeto.
显然我对这个男孩没有任何怨恨，但发生了什么......
Obviously I have nothing against the boy, but what happened...
Obviamente que no tengo nada contra el chico, pero lo que pasó...
他们不喜欢它，他们不喜欢它，因为显然我们从很小的时候就做出了很大的牺牲，他们已经做到了......
They don't like it, they don't like it because obviously we make a very big sacrifice from a very young age, they have done it...
No gusta, no gusta porque obviamente nosotros hacemos un sacrificio muy grande desde muy chicos, lo han hecho...
足球史上有许多足球运动员能够参加甲级联赛的比赛。
Many footballers throughout the history of football to be able to play a match in the first division.
Muchísimos futbolistas en toda la historia del fútbol para poder jugar un partido en primera división.
这种事情一点都不好
this kind of thing is not good at all
este tipo de cosas no es para nada bueno
罗马换帅后你感觉如何？
How are you after the change of coach at Roma?
¿Cómo estás vos después del cambio de entrenador en la Roma?
也许你没有必要在球队中发挥你想要的那么多。
Maybe you haven't had to play as much on the team as you would like.
Quizás no te ha tocado jugar tanto en el equipo como quisieras.
你怎么样，你感觉如何，除了你一直在国家队的事实之外，你是一名球员，现在也是球队的一部分。
How are you, how do you feel, beyond the fact that you are always in the national team, you are a player who is and is part of the team.
cómo estás, cómo te sentís, más allá de que siempre la selección, sos un jugador que está y que es parte del equipo.
不，很好，我很好。
No, fine, I'm fine.
No, bien, yo bien.
我继续以最好的方式进行训练，因为我知道......
I continue training in the best way, knowing that...
Me sigo entrenando de la mejor manera, sabiendo que...
由于教练的性格，上场的可能性就会小很多。
The possibility of playing was going to be much less due to the characteristics of the coach.
la posibilidad de jugar iba a ser mucho menos por la característica del entrenador.
我带着它去训练，为了能够很好地进入国家队，因为对我来说这是当时最重要的事情。
I took it to train, to make it to the national team well, because for me it was the most important thing at that time.
lo tomé para entrenarme, para llegar bien a la selección, porque para mí era lo más importante en ese momento.
我知道我将不得不少踢一些比赛，而且国家队的成绩很接近，但今天
I knew that I was going to have to play a little less and the national team was close, but today
sabía que me iba a tocar jugar un poco menos y la selección estaba cerca, pero hoy en día
我想到了国家队，显然当我回到俱乐部时，我们将有一位新教练，我们会看看会发生什么。
I think about the national team, obviously when I return to the club we will have a new coach and we will see what happens.
Pienso en la selección, obviamente cuando vuelva al club tendremos un entrenador nuevo y veremos qué pasa.
换了场地，他们离开了纪念碑，他们显然会在一个你能想象到的、你很熟悉的球场上比赛。
Change of venue, they leave the Monumental, they are obviously going to play on a court that identifies you a lot, as you imagine.
Cambio de recinto, salen del Monumental, van a jugar obviamente en una cancha que te identifica y mucho, como lo imaginás.
好吧，好吧，我真的很喜欢，我真的很喜欢为国家队效力，穿着这件球衣训练，显然......
Well, well, I really enjoy, I really enjoy playing for the national team, training with this shirt, obviously...
Bien, bien, yo disfruto mucho, disfruto mucho de jugar en la selección, de entrenar con esta camiseta, obviamente que...
使用货币进行交易是一个优势，但是正如我常说的
that playing in the currency is a plus, but well, as I always say
que jugar en la moneda es un plus, pero bueno como digo siempre
在 Bombonera、Monumental 或室内玩耍，对我来说，我都以同样的方式享受它。
Playing in the Bombonera, in the Monumental or playing indoors, for me I enjoy it in the same way.
Jugar en la Bombonera, en el Monumental o jugar en el interior, para mí lo disfruto de la misma manera.
例如，在巴拉圭，他们不允许穿着狮子座衬衫入境。
In Paraguay they do not allow entry, for example, with a Leo shirt.
en Paraguay no permiten entrar por ejemplo con la remera de leo
你知道吗？
Did you know that?
¿Sabías eso?
有一项规定，任何人都不能穿着利奥的衬衫进入。
That there is a measure, that no one can enter with Leo's shirt.
Que hay una medida, que nadie puede entrar con la remera de Leo.
这有什么问题吗？
What's wrong with that?
¿Qué te pasa con eso?
我什么都不知道，我是从你那里才知道的。
I didn't know anything, I just found out from you.
No sabía nada, me acabo de enterar por vos.
但是，嘿，每个人都放自己的东西。
But hey, everyone puts their own things.
Pero bueno, cada uno pone sus cosas.
打他自己的比赛，比如说，在场外，我们会考虑自己。
to play his own game, let's say, off the field and we will think about ourselves.
de hacer su propio juego, digamos, fuera de la cancha y nosotros pensaremos en nosotros.
博卡球迷对罗马教练的变动一定不那么兴奋。
The Boca fan has to be a little less excited about the change of coach in Roma.
Al cambio de técnico en la Roma, al hincha de Boca, lo tiene que ilusionar un poco menos.
我不知道，我不知道，我总是这么说，我过着我的生活和我的事业......
I don't know, I don't know, I always say it, I live my life and my career...
No sé, no sé, yo lo digo siempre, yo vivo mi vida y mi carrera...
显然，每天都有很多人谈论他没有参加比赛的事实等等，但是
day by day obviously there was a lot of talk about the fact that he was not playing and so on but
día a día obviamente que se habló mucho por el tema de que no estaba jugando y demás pero
对我来说最重要的事情就是每天思考我的俱乐部。
The most important thing for me is always to think about the day to day, about my club.
Lo más importante para mí siempre es pensar en el día a día, en mi club.
事实上，在丹尼尔到来之前，我一直很开心。
The truth is that, until Daniel was there, I was very happy.
La verdad es que yo, hasta que estuvo Daniel, estuve muy feliz.
我在一座令人难以置信的城市，在一家壮观的俱乐部，人们非常爱我，所以......
I was in an incredible city, in a spectacular club, people loved me a lot so...
estuve en una ciudad increíble, en un club espectacular, la gente me quería mucho así que...
我很高兴，然后教练就过去了，今天我们把教练换回来，我们看看会发生什么。
I was very happy, then the coach passed, today we change the coach back and we will see what happens.
Estaba muy feliz, después pasó el entrenador, hoy en día cambiamos de vuelta el entrenador y veremos qué pasa.
在博卡，情况也发生了变化。
In Boca it also changed.
En Boca también cambió.
费尔南多，你知道吗，没有接到电话，对吧？
Fernando, you know yourself, there was no call, right?
Fernando, te conoces, no hubo ningún llamado, ¿no?
不，我没有和费说话，我没有和费说话。
No, I didn't talk to Fer, I didn't talk to Fer.
No, no hablé con Fer, no hablé con Fer.
看看他有没有给我打电话。
Let's see if he called me or not.
Vamos a ver si me llamó o no.
谢谢。
Gracias.
我们还将聆听 Valerdi 的现场表演。
We will also be listening to Valerdi live.
Valerdi lo vamos también a estar escuchando en vivo.
几分钟之内。
in a matter of minutes.
en cuestión de minutos.
不，不，不，不，不，不，不，不，不，不，不，不，不，不，不，不，不，不，不，不。
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
我留在那里拉。
I stay there pulling.
Me quedo ahí tirando.
这是运气，这是运气。
It was luck, it was luck.
Fue suerte, fue suerte.
我们进来了，这是件好事，我们赢了，所以这很重要。
We got in, that's the good thing and we won, so it's important.
Se entró, eso es lo bueno y ganamos, así que es importante.
他就这样结束了练习。
He ended practice with that.
Terminó la práctica con eso.
是的，那是金球，它留在那里，我击中了它。
Yes, it was the golden goal and it stayed there and I hit it.
Sí, era el gol de oro y quedó ahí y le pegué.
你和梅西一起踢球，你感染了一点里奥的能力，对吧？
You played with Messi and you infected a little bit of Leo's ability, right?
Juguaste con Messi y contagiaste un poquito de la habilidad de Leo, ¿no?
是的，我想可能就是这样，因为我不知道。
Yeah, I think that might be it, because I don't know.
Sí, creo que puede ser eso, porque no sé.
嗯，小时候我练习过，但是嘿，它卡住了，然后就出来了。
Well, as a kid I practiced, but hey, it stuck and it came out.
Bueno, de chico practicaba, pero bueno, me quedó y salió.
他们告诉你什么了吗？
Did they tell you something?
¿Te dijeron algo?
例如，梅西对你说过什么吗？
For example, did Messi say something to you?
Por ejemplo, Messi ¿te dijo algo?
是的，我们喊进球了，他什么也没说。
Yes, we shouted the goal, he didn't say anything.
Sí, gritamos el gol, no dijo nada.
我也不打算谈论这个。
I'm not going to talk about that either.
Tampoco voy a hablar de eso.
我一团糟地离开了。
I left in a mess.
Salí de pedo.
好吧，有可能在法庭上出现这些现象。
Well, having the possibility of being on a court with these phenomena.
Bueno, tener la posibilidad de estar adentro de una cancha con estos fenómenos.
世界冠军，以及两届冠军美国队，我想对于你来说，你在做什么？
the world champions, with the two-time champions of America, I imagine that for you, what are you doing?
los campeones del mundo, con los bicampeones de América, me imagino que para vos que estás haciendo
你和你最年长的人真正迈出的第一步，这一定是一种奢侈
your first real steps with your oldest this must be a luxury
tus primeros pasos de verdad con la mayor este debe ser un lujazo
是的，这对我来说是一个梦想。
Yes, it's a dream for me.
Sí, es un sueño para mí.
我说过连续来两次还是第一次。
I had said that it is the first time that I have come twice in a row.
Había dicho que es la primera vez que vengo dos seguidas.
这对我个人的信心也有很大帮助。
That also helps me a lot personally in terms of confidence.
Eso a mí también me ayuda mucho a lo personal en cuanto a confianza.
也能进组。
to get into the group too.
a meterme en el grupo también.
为了进入这个小组并达到现有的水平，我必须能够胜任这项任务
to get into this group the level that there is and well I have to be up to the task
meterse en este grupo el nivel que hay y bueno tengo que estar a la altura
并且每次都以更好的方式去做，以便能够继续在那里。
and every time do it in a better way to be able to continue being there.
y cada vez hacerlo de mejor manera para poder seguir estando.
这个群体有什么特别之处？
What is special about this group?
¿Qué tiene de especial este grupo?
我认为心态，心态，继续为事物奋斗的愿望，无论一切都被欺骗得多么严重。
I think the mentality, the mentality, the desire to continue fighting for things, no matter how badly everything has been deceived.
Creo que la mentalidad, la mentalidad, la gana de seguir peleando por cosas, por mal que haya enganado todo.
每次他们进入球场时，他们都会抛下一切，你可以在训练中看到这一点。
that every time they enter a court they leave everything and you can see it in training.
que cada vez que entran a una cancha dejan todo y se puede ver en los entrenamientos.
水平非常高，甚至比在国内、有时在俱乐部还要高。
The level is very high, even higher than at home, sometimes in the clubs.
El nivel es altísimo, incluso más que en mi casa, a veces, en los clubes.
来到这里...
Coming here...
Venir acá...
需求、质量、一切都总是更上一层楼。
It is always one more step of demand, of quality, of everything.
es un pasito más siempre de exigencia, de calidad, de todo.
里奥，你必须和委内瑞拉队比赛，你表现得很好，这些都是你必须利用的时刻，因为这是第一次轮到我。
Leo, you had to play with Venezuela, you did well, those are the moments that you have to take advantage of because it's the first time it's my turn.
Leo, te tocó jugar con Venezuela, lo hiciste bien, esos son los momentos que hay que aprovechar porque es la primera vez que me toca.
连续两次在那里，我的意思是，也许没有太多，因为基地总是被维护，但必须利用这些可能性。
being twice in a row, I mean, maybe there is not much because a base is always maintained but those possibilities must be taken advantage of.
estar dos veces seguidas, digo, quizás no hay demasiado porque siempre se mantiene una base pero esas posibilidades hay que aprovecharlas.
是的，由于他们所取得的成就，基地得以维持是正常的，是的，正如你所说。
Yes, it is normal that the base is maintained due to the achievements they have made and yes, as you say.
Sí, es normal que la base se mantenga por los logros que han hecho y sí, como decís vos.
我必须抓住每一个机会。
Every opportunity I get I have to take advantage of.
cada oportunidad que me toque tengo que aprovecharla.
准备好并达到标准。
prepared and up to par.
preparado y a la altura.
我没想到与委内瑞拉的比赛有什么好处。
I didn't expect the good thing about the match with Venezuela.
Lo bueno del partido con Venezuela no me lo esperaba.
Leo 给我打电话，我必须快速进去，我什至都无法热身。
Leo called me and I had to go in quickly, I couldn't even warm up.
Me llamó Leo y tuve que entrar rápido, no pude ni entrar en calor.
但好消息是结果很好，我希望现在有时间并以一种很好的方式去做。
but the good thing is that it turned out well and I hope to have the minute now and do it in a great way.
pero lo bueno es que salió bien y espero tener el minuto ahora y hacerlo de gran manera.
作为一个受人尊敬的足球运动员，你将自己融入团队是什么感觉？你让他们接近你，你走，你采取主动。
Like a respectful footballer, what is it like for you to insert yourself into the group? You let them approach you, you go, you take the initiative.
como un futbolista respetuoso cómo es puntualmente para vos la inserción en el grupo dejás que se acerquen ellos vas vos tomás la iniciativa
显然我会尝试留出空间然后适应。
I obviously try to leave space and then adapt.
Trato obviamente de dejarse espacio y después ir adaptándome.
如果他们跟我说话，如果没有，参与也没有多大关系。
If they talk to me, if not, getting involved doesn't matter much.
Si me hablan, si no, ir metiéndome da poco.
没有不尊重，但他们也提供了很多帮助。
without disrespect, but they also help a lot.
sin faltar respeto, pero también ayudan mucho ellos.
前队友，我和他们中的一些人一起在 U-20 踢球，我有很好的氛围，所以这也有帮助。
former teammate, I played in the U-20 with some of them and I have good vibes, so that also helps.
ex compañero, jugué en el sub-20 con algunos y tengo buena onda, entonces eso también ayuda.
我们在 Barrenechea 旁边介绍。
We present next to Barrenechea.
presentamos al lado de Barrenechea.
关于他，你能告诉我们什么吗？
What can you tell us about him?
¿Qué nos podés contar de él?
正如我所见，他显然迈出了第一步。
As I have seen him obviously taking his first steps.
Como lo he visto obviamente dando sus primeros pasos.
我在西托身上看到了这一点。
I see it well in Xito.
Lo veo bien en Xito.
在去库迪亚之前我和他一起踢过球。
I played with him before going to Cúdia.
Jugué con él antes de ir al Cúdia.
不幸的是他被排除在外了。
Unfortunately he was left out.
Lamentablemente él quedó afuera.
但是嘿，我看过他打球，我们有同一个代表，所以我关注恩佐。
But hey, I've seen him play, we have the same representative, so I follow Enzo.
Pero bueno, yo lo he visto jugar, tenemos el mismo representante, entonces lo sigo a Enzo.
我知道他的品质，他的比赛方式，我非常喜欢。
I know the quality he has, the way he plays and I like it a lot.
Sé la calidad que tiene, la forma de jugar y a mí me gusta mucho.
他是我非常喜欢的球员，我希望他能在这里展示出来。
He is a player that I really like and I hope he can show it here.
Es un jugador que me gusta mucho y espero que lo pueda demostrar acá.
就在那里！
There it was!
¡Ahí estaba!